beat beat beat beat
Funky drum beat and whistle
Wiggle your body... and don't forget to freeze!
Shake your little shoulders, shake your little knees,
Blow around like autumn leaves in the breeze!
Jump up high, touch the ceiling and the floor,
Run in place, run a little bit more!
Now listen closely, stop in your track...
Three, two, one... FREEZE like a statue back!
Sudden silence for 2 beats
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, dance all around!
Stomp your feet upon the ground!
Wiggle to the left, wiggle to the right,
Dancing with all your might!
Spin like a top, spinning round and round,
Tiptoe softly without making a sound!
Flap your arms like an eagle in the sky,
Wave both hands up way up high!
Get ready, get steady, hold your pose...
Three, two, one... FREEZE and touch your nose!
Sudden silence for 2 beats
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, dance all around!
Stomp your feet upon the ground!
Wiggle to the left, wiggle to the right,
Dancing with all your might!
You didn't move! You win!
Everybody sit down and breathe